{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"adab851b-2824-44fe-8f09-44fbc89b1fc2"},"exam":{"id":"112eda13-f7f8-41fc-a5cd-d8e5c973e99c","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"3617c0aa-2fa9-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"For enhanced technical support, some AWS Support plans enable you to have an unlimited number of contacts that can open an unlimited amount of cases. Which of the following choices offer this feature?","explanation":"With either the Business or Enterprise support plan, you can provide have an unlimited number of contacts that can open an unlimited amount of cases.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false}]},{"id":"5ca8852d-519a-409a-b998-d74eb78ef5cf","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are Amazon EFS (Elastic File Storage) storage classes?","explanation":"There are two Amazon EFS storage classes, which are Standard and Infrequent Access. One Zone – Infrequent Access, Intelligent Tiering, and Deep Glacier are names specifically for Amazon S3 storage classes.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/efs/latest/ug/whatisefs.html","title":"What Is Amazon Elastic File System?"}],"answers":[{"id":"eb6d8ae6f20283755b339c0dc273988b","text":"Standard","correct":true},{"id":"9f0832b6670166f059cfdc8dc49133b4","text":"One Zone - Infrequent Access","correct":false},{"id":"72156eca90dac061dfd0a6da22c5e9b0","text":"Deep Glacier","correct":false},{"id":"b1926a8ac417114ef193a282594538c7","text":"Infrequent Access","correct":true},{"id":"13c28d56109c12a096b5e325b65a1c01","text":"Intelligent Tiering","correct":false}]},{"id":"d05a0228-8d82-4cef-8dfb-4e2cb3856a9f","domain":"security","question":"According to the Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is AWS responsible for?","explanation":"Protecting the infrastructure that runs all of the services in the AWS Cloud is the responsibility of AWS. Such services include EC2 infrastructure - the hardware compute platform for running EC2 instances and Amazon Virtual Private Cloud, or VPC, which enables customers to provision a logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud to launch their resources. The subnets, security groups, and network access control lists configured in the VPC are the responsibility of the customer.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/vpc/","title":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"28aaf85b7ba1e63aa22c1c645a4c22e4","text":"Elastic Cloud Compute (EC2) infrastructure","correct":true},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"c33dcb724e4d74e54dbc8347d4402690","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud","correct":true},{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false}]},{"id":"wfisjo0f-usp3-160k-im9l-di4ay4ny42e8","domain":"tech","question":"Which AWS service is specifically designed to assist you in processing large data sets?","explanation":"Elastic Map Reduce (EMR) is a service that makes it easy to process large amounts of data efficiently. Redshift is a data warehousing solution. ElastiCache is used for caching data in memory for high speed read-access. EC2 is a general purpose compute service for hosting virtual servers. Whilst you could run big data processing tasks on EC2, it will be easier on EMR, which has been designed specifically for this purpose","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/emr/","title":"About EMR"}],"answers":[{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":false},{"id":"50848259480914860b338e7baf94c29a","text":"ElastiCache","correct":false},{"id":"be94b3c024501e2d7e9e64f4e0d18af9","text":"Elastic Map Reduce (EMR)","correct":true},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false}]},{"id":"1cfba8e0-0fb8-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"billing","question":"You have EC2 and RDS instances, Redshift and Elasticsearch clusters, and an SNS topic in your AWS environment. Which of these services support reserved pricing?","explanation":"Amazon SNS is the only one of the five mentioned services that does not have reserved pricing. On the other hand, Amazon EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch do.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/pricing/","title":"Amazon RDS Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/pricing/","title":"Amazon Redshift Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticsearch-service/pricing/","title":"Amazon Elasticsearch Service Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"9d6fbf729ccc02278cc50176a91ed3fe","text":"EC2, Redshift, and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"fcb02ff285a97f0ed386c6cfe36b02f4","text":"EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch","correct":true},{"id":"3ec389f2e16e0e0443f3ef49d2b58d05","text":"EC2 and RDS","correct":false},{"id":"0221d4f5950f35dfcf98f6a60f60d20d","text":" Elasticsearch and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"65e4dd05e0a1392e55661f27717e96cb","text":"RDS, Redshift, Elasticsearch, and SNS","correct":false}]},{"id":"caa31392-2fbc-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following engines are classified as relational databases on AWS?","explanation":"Amazon Aurora, Microsoft SQL Server, and MariaDB are three types of RDS engines on AWS. By contrast, DynamoDB is Amazon’s nonrelational database solution.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/","title":"Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"7f9733e208088b1ce6df3d4be1765396","text":"MariaDB","correct":true},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"69670a9d53817d1ec89e685997343ce2","text":"Amazon Aurora","correct":true},{"id":"78898e52fcbdc5337204a384f2456d4f","text":"Microsoft SQL Server","correct":true}]},{"id":"rku8juy8-m8eo-xhrd-ap7e-a3nhr9045k2l","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below is TRUE when considering subnets in a VPC?","explanation":"By default, all subnets within a VPC can communicate with each other, without needing any other resources or configuration. NAT Gateway and Internet Gateway work in different scenarios to allow your subnet to communicate with the internet and are not required to communicate between subnets","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonVPC/latest/UserGuide/VPC_Subnets.html","title":"VPCs and Subnets"}],"answers":[{"id":"b5bcf23beb0bab6ed020ef6e8d9026ef","text":"Subnets within a VPC can only communicate with each other if a NAT Gateway is deployed","correct":false},{"id":"ecfdf4b74c36d8d497f1023a5b24e38f","text":"Subnets within a VPC can only communicate with each other if an Internet Gateway is deployed","correct":false},{"id":"8ff25f40e9a121e4620e1809190ac599","text":"By default, subnets within a VPC cannot communicate with each other","correct":false},{"id":"bdcce4ddcc3bbe6bca2d1851d91ff3a2","text":"By default, all subnets within a VPC can communicate with each other","correct":true}]},{"id":"ef918c09-219a-45b3-b1cc-f5b02cdbfc1d","domain":"concepts","question":"What type of placement group should you use to spread Amazon EC2 instances across logical partitions so that they don’t share the same underlying hardware?","explanation":"With a partition placement group, EC2 instances are placed into logical segments called partitions, each of which has its own set of racks to supply its network and power source. This level of isolation is designed to prevent the impact of hardware failure within your application.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/placement-groups.html","title":"Placement Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"249694a485fc5d3289c38986b4f8e887","text":"Cluster","correct":false},{"id":"3349300356cb3141ea939dcbdf749789","text":"Partition","correct":true},{"id":"66f9c6c5b672ee16deeef6e4503cb4bc","text":"Reserve","correct":false},{"id":"180bc3b1c5619aaef40e803f49921012","text":"Spread","correct":false}]},{"id":"0mdd9dnl-ji3o-hjum-lyr4-wtpoks65v0z9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements about AWS Region is true?","explanation":"A region is a geographical area divided into Availability Zones. Each region contains at least two publicly accessible Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"bec481a5e2c63bfc93d4922d5845bd2b","text":"Regions are only available in some locations globally","correct":false},{"id":"2cf30d8c571fe080cdd53d0a78db5689","text":"Regions are automatically fully synchronized to contain the same data globally","correct":false},{"id":"1c52cae4b07ea355b6bf0d1522efc7e7","text":"Regions are made up of Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"fddc13d769887bc62fc14c8d844e1aa9","text":"Regions are generally specific geographical areas","correct":true}]},{"id":"e5705f98-2edd-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following falls under the AWS database services category?","explanation":"ElastiCache, which serves as Amazon’s in-memory data store, is the only AWS database service listed here. The others are AWS storage services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/","title":"Amazon Web Services (AWS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"df346128c45efa43efc29607224fc716","text":"Amazon Simple Storage Service (S3)","correct":false},{"id":"4b21f5ceb7fb3f03f0d53a427f6be836","text":"Amazon FSx","correct":false},{"id":"d2a6652ddeb631da029d1f2806e11fdc","text":"Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)","correct":false},{"id":"770b120ec487568871cc9ab64475af46","text":"Amazon ElastiCache","correct":true}]},{"id":"1a184992-2fe5-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are advantages of using Amazon Machine Images (AMIs) backed by Amazon Elastic Block Storage (EBS), rather than by Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2) instance storage?","explanation":"When launching an EC2 instance, Amazon EBS speeds up the process over the EC2 instance storage. In addition, EBS uses persistent storage, which means that the data will be retained despite instance stops, terminations, or hardware failures. EC2 instance storage is ephemeral, which means data is lost when an instance is stopped, terminated of fails.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/RootDeviceStorage.html","title":"Amazon EC2 Root Device Volume"}],"answers":[{"id":"6bc959028a0d1f69905507976853f2a2","text":"EBS launches faster than EC2 instance storage.","correct":true},{"id":"cb69533987635ed7b48a30fb480be74c","text":"EBS is memory-optimized.","correct":false},{"id":"0102366a40ae9c7c88ef2d94a1b441ed","text":"EBS offers more storage space.","correct":false},{"id":"6650a3b982bb9d582cf6cbdfa6218802","text":"Unlike EC2 instance store, EBS uses persistent storage.","correct":true}]},{"id":"86d0ccb9-ab67-4952-a7ea-0fea12fc6c1f","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE statements when it comes to data security in AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service - which includes security. The customer is responsible for who can access the data itself.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"599dca975551e5a41106ce454a46e4e0","text":"AWS is responsible for the security of the hardware the data resides on","correct":true},{"id":"7a0bc438686e10d5e1ab102d0dc0e4a9","text":"The customer is responsible for the security of the software that manages the data","correct":false},{"id":"6e8271456f0c471167caae0d75aab487","text":"The customer is responsible for the security of the hardware the data resides on","correct":false},{"id":"2844802845f801aded529f1d22c63d82","text":"AWS is responsible for the security of the software that manages the data","correct":true},{"id":"9f02eb6c8050b89db31831403951787b","text":"The customer is responsible for managing who can access the data","correct":true},{"id":"0ed894aaf38bd44ba33d1612854617d0","text":"AWS is responsible for managing who can access the data","correct":false}]},{"id":"alwhmkiv-aa40-zbsb-1app-zkbeiem7zvs3","domain":"concepts","question":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, for which of the following does AWS not assume responsibility?","explanation":"Customers are responsible for their own customer data in the cloud. AWS manages the Networking, Hypervisor Configuration, and Physical Security","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS shared Responsibility"}],"answers":[{"id":"a5fa5746370b608090b994a97b49e98b","text":"Networking","correct":false},{"id":"5dd5aedeaa5de8a95f383a8e014b1e5d","text":"Physical security of AWS facilities","correct":false},{"id":"6016c2bb7bd8dd79293094d37ebfea3f","text":"Customer data","correct":true},{"id":"1b837a3c0786d704da0c00c61b4d57b5","text":"Hypervisors","correct":false}]},{"id":"97909ec2-34ad-4743-b7cc-ca2c83c62cc1","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following statements are true of the AWS Free Tier?","explanation":"The AWS Free Tier offers some services for free for the first 12 months after signing up for an AWS account. It also offers free trials of select AWS services for a short period. So, usage is governed by these principles. Although there are some service usages that are always free, this does not apply to EC2 Micro instances nor S3 storage of up to 5 GB.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"c90c4c865ee803cfa9bbe8e9a2d845c9","text":"Amazon S3 storage of up to 5 GB is always free.","correct":false},{"id":"424553c7a1502a98737dfd15823ee215","text":"Some AWS services are free for the first 12 months following the initial sign-up date to AWS.","correct":true},{"id":"f60585d833d73cf82fda96da1f19b3e6","text":"Some AWS services come with short-term free trial offers.","correct":true},{"id":"42c6d3d9032dba4f7aea8ddeedde2f6c","text":"You will never be charged for use of EC2 Micro instances.","correct":false}]},{"id":"csqz3fzq-fvxm-wmtm-lq03-1qm6tx6rsm40","domain":"tech","question":"When you upload an object to S3 storage - where will AWS keep it?","explanation":"Any object uploaded to S3 is automatically stored in multiple Availability Zones in the Region in which it was uploaded. This means that if any single AZ in a Region is experiencing issues, objects stored in S3 will still be available. Although objects in S3 can be made to be accessible globally, by default they are always stored in a redundant fashion in only the region they were uploaded, ruling out the other answers.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/","title":"About S3"}],"answers":[{"id":"d4e7f5d03f7a64d82b49ae9aa1f01716","text":"In multiple Regions across the globe.","correct":false},{"id":"8739ddb65808177938fb8b26c3bede98","text":"In AWS's central global storage site in the us-east-1 Region","correct":false},{"id":"e134be4f4ec87c7e4b3a807a60f8332c","text":"In a single, central location within the Region you select.","correct":false},{"id":"2d3a21e9924efc0317a134b857ee4036","text":"In multiple Availability Zones within the Region you select.","correct":true}]},{"id":"a1237c57-f005-8048-710c-489f984ca8d0","domain":"tech","question":"Where would you find the AWS Attestation of Compliance Documentation for PCI DSS?","explanation":"AWS Artifact is your go-to, central resource for compliance-related information that matters to you. It provides on-demand access to AWS’ security and compliance reports and select online agreements. AWS Support's site provides general information about compliance, but does not hold the secure reports or certificates. AWS IAM is used to control security within your AWS Account. Amazon Macie is a data security classification service.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/artifact/","title":"AWS Artifact"}],"answers":[{"id":"73bf7f67bbb8ede06c6d98f4133f9743","text":"AWS Identity and Access Management","correct":false},{"id":"1f7efb5a61d1162575c83917dd086ad7","text":"Amazon Macie","correct":false},{"id":"26e8220e8fac28d2a1a9a18ca81aabd7","text":"AWS Support","correct":false},{"id":"60b018772cea138af5a8c452ed694734","text":"AWS Artifact","correct":true}]},{"id":"e4306810-2a64-4eb4-9c58-431ea8a91190","domain":"tech","question":"A software development team needs to create numerous testing environments each day based on multiple concurrent project activities. Provisioning of these environments needs to happen within minutes to ensure that project deadlines are met. The number of environments needed daily varies depending shifting priorities in business requirements. How can the team best achieve the agility they need for creating the testing environments?","explanation":"AWS CloudFormation provides templates to specify all the AWS resources needed by the testing environments. These templates can be instantiated as stacks to provision consistent environments every time one is needed. AWS Auto Scaling will only handle the EC2 instances, and expands and contracts instances based on policies. AWS Systems Manager is useful for system administration tasks, and AWS Lambda has run-time limitations.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudformation/","title":"AWS CloudFormation"}],"answers":[{"id":"d0251c104fe180cf808a23905d11ab7c","text":"Leverage AWS Auto Scaling to expand and contract the testing server pool based on demand","correct":false},{"id":"5a6510861bc8f77b0a75412925312eff","text":"Invoke AWS Lambda functions to run the test scenarios","correct":false},{"id":"7eab42e9ed95a6b8f6eba51c1d6ba41e","text":"Have AWS CloudFormation provision the stacks and resources needed for the testing environments","correct":true},{"id":"d9a6df6805662c26de87001a1d7b5ae4","text":"Use AWS Systems Manager Automation to provision and de-provision the testing environments","correct":false}]},{"id":"9da21f94-7d9e-4bcf-8c7c-fc97b0634977","domain":"security","question":"Your company has updated its security policies to include cloud workloads as well as those running on-premises. Your manager would like a report of which technologies will require configuration changes. Which of the following will not be included in the report because they are the responsibility of AWS?","explanation":"In the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, AWS in responsible for managing host operating systems. Users are responsible for managing guest operating systems, as well as Security Group Firewalls, Amazon Aurora data encryption, and S3 access control lists.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"8061595e3a5f2fb2195dd627dd35f5d2","text":"Host operating systems","correct":true},{"id":"331bd4e2a8ab147e5a6a47e5b9c40d65","text":"S3 Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"64f8358ae4360eddd993acde2d19789c","text":"Amazon Aurora data encryption","correct":false},{"id":"63c21f07ff59add0f7e474ef5ec57c2e","text":"Security Group firewalls","correct":false}]},{"id":"b6f1e02c-1a49-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements is true of AWS CloudTrail?","explanation":"CloudTrail is actually enabled automatically when you create an AWS account. The other three responses are correct.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awscloudtrail/latest/userguide/how-cloudtrail-works.html","title":"How CloudTrail Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"38105bf4ed77d230d01428de259f3ea0","text":"By default, CloudTrail event log files are encrypted using Amazon S3 server-side encryption.","correct":true},{"id":"c4817f75e8865468e0d6688b3f7fa9ae","text":"CloudTrail delivers log files within 15 minutes of account activity.","correct":true},{"id":"d70f308061c9f3b0aef10fe5b3a954ab","text":"With CloudTrail, you can create a trail that either applies to one Region or to all Regions.","correct":true},{"id":"98be3a0e01d49274c41618e1b43ff9c5","text":"When you create an AWS account, you will have to manually enable CloudTrail.","correct":false}]},{"id":"1978e26b-04e4-45ca-8a47-205e50d96c7f","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Regions contain two or more Availability Zones, which are themselves made up of one or more Datacentres. Edge locations are a part of AWS' content distribution network, and are seperate from Regions and AZs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"988326895b235b7a5f2b7eea1a9838f5","text":"Regions contain Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"23b72701776466936b717d47eb3be164","text":"Availability Zones contain Data Centres","correct":true},{"id":"22d0cb7092012aea1123fcbd58c6519c","text":"Data Centres contain Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"cd6f4614de9281b97b511a1f3f534e8c","text":"Edge Locations contain Availability Zones","correct":false}]},{"id":"5a168390-1f66-11ea-a5e8-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"You added a recently hired HR Assistant to the IAM group named 'HumanResources'. Which of the following statements will apply to that user?","explanation":"By adding the HR Assistant to the 'HumanResources' group by using the AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) service, the new hiree is now a member of the company’s HR department and inherits the administrative permissions of that group.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/getting-started_create-admin-group.html","title":"Create Your First IAM Admin User and Group"}],"answers":[{"id":"367051fc494f2dba53682af0d5f9a9e1","text":"The HR Assistant becomes the AWS root account user.","correct":false},{"id":"4f98907d2b5e12fad173f30f4d61ec84","text":"The HR Assistant inherits the permissions of the 'HumanResources' group.","correct":true},{"id":"a445a3cad5d84550114916ae6df763c4","text":"The HR Assistant becomes leader of the Human Resources department.","correct":false},{"id":"b098a137cb3a11528e46deb8c5aff98d","text":"The HR Assistant becomes an IAM member of the company’s Human Resources department.","correct":true}]},{"id":"cd73d505-c09a-44cb-a7fa-0ac6be0f5c99","domain":"tech","question":"Upon attempting to create an additional S3 bucket, you realize that you have reached your S3 bucket limit in your AWS account. You anticipate creating even more S3 buckets in the future for your photos and documents. Which of the following is the quickest solution?","explanation":"The key word here is 'quickest'. Granted, you can delete the S3 buckets of your choice, and you can try consolidating files into select buckets and deleting the emptied ones. But that could be quite a hassle to do, compared to simply requesting a service limit increase at the AWS Support Center. By default, you can create up to 100 buckets in an AWS account, and that is a limit that AWS does not override without officially requesting for a service limit increase.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/BucketRestrictions.html","title":"Bucket Restrictions and Limitations"}],"answers":[{"id":"e7b93b6f7bea9c58f27912c7974c74d4","text":"Submit a service limit increase.","correct":true},{"id":"104e2902668d313ccfbc1bc78457e84d","text":"Delete the S3 buckets that you barely use.","correct":false},{"id":"46bca3e00e40780aa04c28899f5bbe6b","text":"Simply create the S3 bucket; AWS will automatically override the bucket limit.","correct":false},{"id":"340d5ba6fcedb315c6adee97b1239f3f","text":"Consolidate files into half of the S3 buckets and delete the empty ones.","correct":false}]},{"id":"8d9bfa67-4685-4ba8-a5a7-d0518daba638","domain":"billing","question":"If you want access to all AWS Trusted Advisor checks, which of these support plans will provide that?","explanation":"You must choose either the Business or Enterprise support plan to gain access to all AWS Trusted Advisor checks.","links":[{"url":"https://console.aws.amazon.com/support/plans/home?#/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false}]},{"id":"b419a913-a5f1-4ad2-8c06-3b579643d073","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following is AWS responsible for in the Shared Responsibility Model?","explanation":"AWS manages security of the cloud. This includes the infrastructure, which consists of regions, edge locations, and Availability Zones. On the other hand, security in the cloud is the responsibility of the customer. Therefore, AWS is not responsible for safeguarding customer data; the customer is.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":true},{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"0b4219abe92a5981f2c74b7a4ec441ab","text":"Customer Data","correct":false},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":true}]},{"id":"3ygeb7pi-gjw6-mzi9-0kq5-03x2sygemst0","domain":"tech","question":"What happens when an RDS Master database in a Multi-AZ deployment goes down?","explanation":"Amazon RDS automatically performs a failover in the event of Loss of availability in primary Availability Zone, Loss of network connectivity to primary, Compute unit failure on primary, or Storage failure on primary","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/details/multi-az/#Failover_conditions","title":"Amazon RDS Multi-AZ Failover"}],"answers":[{"id":"6e8a400152e499f96063d91a9447d9c2","text":"You must copy the attached EBS volume to the standby.","correct":false},{"id":"84e57d062c135e5df249a3e13b35780b","text":"You must use the AWS console to promote the standby to Master.","correct":false},{"id":"6e0895c1d81409b9b1ea4c57b6022eba","text":"The asynchronous replication of RDS Multi-AZ deployments means you will suffer some data loss.","correct":false},{"id":"b650a48a49e9b851bc85cc3720ef42f4","text":"RDS automatically fails over to the standby, which is promoted to Master.","correct":true}]},{"id":"yvxo9l3i-wh4o-2dqm-3mnu-snzqe8qbcn6w","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes an AWS Region?","explanation":"A Region is a distinct location within a geographic area designed to provide high availability to a specific geography. Regions are a key concept in AWS' Global Infrastructure - each is made up of one or more isolated (within that region) Availability Zones. There are often multiple AWS Regions on each continent, such as North America","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"1230f90d0fb76db29194467e14f8e099","text":"A collection of databases that can only be accessed from a specific geographic region.","correct":false},{"id":"8c91beabafc69d771d60455febdc0927","text":"A console that gives you a quick, global picture of your cloud computing environment.","correct":false},{"id":"cd212d0c12772fef24104f0585e29933","text":"A collection of data centres that are spread evenly around a specific continent.","correct":false},{"id":"02994d9c387a384eeaa6efd09a6dd102","text":"A distinct location within a geographic area designed to provide high availability to a specific geography.","correct":true}]},{"id":"og6hjhzz-5hd0-yz2y-lhcp-id573kosdzz0","domain":"security","question":"When talking about AWS security, what does \"Authentication\" refer to?","explanation":"Authentication identifies who is accessing the system and passes that information to the authorization process, which in turn determines what permissions the user has in AWS. Although Authentication is the first part of the process to log in to the console, by itself it it is not enough.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/details/manage-users/","title":"Managing Users with IAM"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction.html","title":"IAM - authenticated vs. authorized "}],"answers":[{"id":"2fd83b869d1e9b4e9cb436b10c4dd876","text":"Logging in to the console","correct":false},{"id":"0159ee609574fa72f3ce74e9f9acae98","text":"Evaluating what permissions a user has","correct":false},{"id":"14f566a413faf99b530a23db8794522d","text":"A user delegating access to another user temporarily","correct":false},{"id":"1f8db5b38e9eb894bac42c8cfcc958a8","text":"Identifying who is accessing the system","correct":true}]},{"id":"w5gffphd-hr0c-k6ie-54pn-4jmfwjc6h2bx","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below are load balancer types that AWS offers?","explanation":"Valid load balancer types on AWS are Classic, Network and Application. Service, Web, Database and are not available types, however one of the valid types can be configured for these purposes.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticloadbalancing/","title":"Elastic Load Balancing"}],"answers":[{"id":"e307db07b3975fef922a80d07455ee5e","text":"Database","correct":false},{"id":"0a52da7a03a6de3beefe54f8c03ad80d","text":"Original","correct":false},{"id":"e498749f3c42246d50b15c81c101d988","text":"Application","correct":true},{"id":"d35b51b639528d580362ca7042de6a0e","text":"Classic","correct":true},{"id":"c2ba7e785c49050f48da9aacc45c2b85","text":"Service","correct":false},{"id":"c6e190b284633c48e39e55049da3cce8","text":"Web","correct":false},{"id":"eec89088ee408b80387155272b113256","text":"Network","correct":true}]},{"id":"2d6841a4-2163-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"In AWS, you can stop or terminate instances when not in use. Which of the following concepts describes this capability?","explanation":"Elasticity denotes the ability to increase or reduce the number or capabilities of AWS resources when needed. In this case, stopping or terminating instances means that you are reducing the number of AWS resources used in your environment.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":true},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"857defc5b4c6f1fef867a03c300bdd29","text":"Loose Coupling","correct":false},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false}]},{"id":"84676206-45b7-4b8d-b856-91c915e8d017","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS service usages is free for the first 12 months after signup for an AWS account?","explanation":"Upon signup for an AWS account, you get 750 hours of Amazon EC2 t2.micro instance usage per month for the first 12 months.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"267c5706cefc5dc9fb06ecdab987b079","text":"1 million API Gateway calls received per month","correct":false},{"id":"159df35cfb0a136f46cbecfe096e2468","text":"750 hours of Amazon EC2 t2.micro instance usage per month","correct":true},{"id":"af41413a0bb72142c1ce2257ac3a184f","text":"1 million AWS Lambda requests per month","correct":false},{"id":"02cbe76727c54b36b3ff3915aa629fae","text":"25 GB of Amazon DynamoDB storage","correct":false}]},{"id":"pdd3afvz-mr6t-zycv-zdle-ceeorrmdl4o9","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the AWS Risk and Compliance Program?","explanation":"Control Environment, Risk Management and Information Security are all components of the AWS Risk and Compliance Program. Control Environment includes policies, processes and control activities that are in place to secure the delivery of AWS’ service offerings. AWS management has developed a strategic business plan which includes risk identification and the implementation of controls to mitigate or manage risks as part of the Risk Management component. AWS has implemented a formal information security program designed to protect the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of customers’ systems and data.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/compliance/AWS_Risk_and_Compliance_Whitepaper.pdf","title":"AWS Risk and Compliance"}],"answers":[{"id":"7228bb53bb7855d458965d2f15fc6cd7","text":"Risk Management","correct":true},{"id":"74f53be5e22fad65f914f82977df2447","text":"Control Environment","correct":true},{"id":"0889f4cee1d9f42ae2c1daf686377de0","text":"Information Security","correct":true},{"id":"66216159eaf3a0abb2752836096f99e9","text":"Security Principles","correct":false},{"id":"0719bdee85b7a37d4e74a9d542d24861","text":" Physical Security","correct":false},{"id":"b8aba77333d3fc881739506fee08811c","text":"Environment Automation","correct":false},{"id":"791716f366839a73d41b8ac1ae95bad0","text":"Identity and Access Management","correct":false}]},{"id":"f3458221-d64a-4bbb-b337-65aa47b1614e","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following does Amazon assure will happen when paying for AWS on an as-needed basis?","explanation":"Amazon provides certain benefits when you pay for services on an as-needed basis for your business. You can spend more time innovating and inventing, which consequently reduces the complexity of procurement and enables your business to be fully elastic. ","links":[{"url":"https://d0.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws_pricing_overview.pdf","title":"How AWS Pricing Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"48a2453a766bcd12a90a271271ca86a5","text":"Redirecting focus to innovation and invention","correct":true},{"id":"4657fb4ee914ab51c07ee5913b69cb48","text":"Reducing procurement complexity","correct":true},{"id":"805b488dc48f4591141569966cee0a89","text":"Enabling the full elasticity of business operations","correct":true},{"id":"8c0088e02946138166ef2d9e4bf9ab82","text":"Spending less money in the long term","correct":false},{"id":"d2c91d7ba7466b41bdbcd42e13db2ecb","text":"Spending more money in the long term","correct":false}]},{"id":"1ad299fd-63d9-4a60-9949-d88b086002cf","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE when running a database in an EC2 Instance?","explanation":"In this case - as the database is being run in an EC2 instance, all aspects of database updates and access is the responsibility of the customer. Similarly as it is and EC2 instance, the customer is responsible for OS patching. Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service - which in this case is the EC2 instance - anything to do with the instance itself is the responsibility of the customer ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"9f9f41256e31feca524f1209e25d70fa","text":"The customer is responsible for updating the database software","correct":true},{"id":"42d5fd24fef6883fb899e3afd050b5a5","text":"The customer is responsible for updating the operating system","correct":true},{"id":"52f2eff0e91b46fe3007ca238393c185","text":"The customer is responsible for managing access to the database","correct":true},{"id":"c7098373cbee0fc9617269a6d3765dd4","text":"AWS is responsible for updating the database software","correct":false},{"id":"199f4eaff96b0da13d07770ee0ff2ab4","text":"AWS is responsible for managing access to the database","correct":false},{"id":"0d6e04dd939a298f20dd927b2a10aa7c","text":"AWS is responsible for updating the operating system","correct":false}]},{"id":"ej2zjxm0-a6xk-q2af-mol8-3c9zwje8qxyh","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support plans features a < 4-hour response time in the event of an impaired production system?","explanation":"Both the Business and Enterprise support levels offer a < 4-hour response time in the event of an impaired production system. Developer is < 12-hour response time in case of any system impairment. Basic does not offer any support for system impairment. Individual is not a real support plan","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"2dd4472245a696bc0b4b944db2a8b519","text":"Individual","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false}]},{"id":"f9bc3071-e017-426b-bb59-bebf2bb60194","domain":"billing","question":"You need an AWS support plan for your production workloads, but want to keep costs to a minimum. Which of the following plans should you choose?","explanation":"The Business Support plan is specifically designed for production workloads in AWS. On one end, Basic Support is included for all AWS customers, and Developer Support plan is best suited for experimenting or testing in AWS. On the other end, there’s the Enterprise Support plan, which is ideal for business and mission-critical workloads.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":false}]},{"id":"i24lu8u9-bdxm-hnxr-9xkq-ogorvl1cou1f","domain":"tech","question":"In which of the following is CloudFront content cached?","explanation":"Edge Locations consist of over 200+ points of presence around the world which provide fast entry into Amazon's global network. Because of how widespread they are, users can connect to their nearest Edge Location, and have their traffic sent through Amazon's fast Global Network to reach the resources it needs sooner. This is how CloudFront's caching mechanism works. There are far less Availability Zones and Regions than Edge Locations, which is why CloudFront does not use them for caching content.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/","title":"About CloudFront"}],"answers":[{"id":"f447ac856e7e72435904956e3b15f433","text":"Region","correct":false},{"id":"47df2b78ac4b3edfbf1c6d0b2a64c579","text":"Data Center","correct":false},{"id":"ec50121a3fdd0fb561e14291a5741b6e","text":"Edge Location","correct":true},{"id":"e95464b98c902ebad35546ca12a620a4","text":"Availability Zone","correct":false}]},{"id":"719cc66e-ayev-f5lb-zoet-xaar4i1a3kub","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following EC2 options is best for long-term workloads with predictable usage patterns?","explanation":"Reserved instances are the most economical option for long-term workloads with predictable usage patterns - in this consumption method, you commit to using resources for a period of time for a reduced cost. On-Demand is great for when you don't have predictable patterns as you only pay for when you are using the resources. Spot works when your workload is interruptible and doesn't need to be available all the time.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/reserved-instances/","title":"Amazon EC2 Reserved Instances"}],"answers":[{"id":"bad26119751b8bdb0b46bff9a096f500","text":"On-Demand instances","correct":false},{"id":"bcc129e8d9496a05a331c903d4c5bcb0","text":"Reserved instances","correct":true},{"id":"ead2a4026c18cbaca9c93c0974c23f89","text":"Dedicated Host","correct":false},{"id":"991236e27b7cb98a2eeff8897b3e0bb4","text":"Spot instances","correct":false}]},{"id":"768b0aa8-1fea-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon sign-up of an AWS account, how much Amazon S3 Standard storage will you get for no cost?","explanation":"When you sign up for an AWS account, you will get 5 GB of standard S3 storage for the first 12 months under the AWS Free Tier.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"074c2f1dacf9047766e7f8d5dce71060","text":"5 GB","correct":true},{"id":"b3dd42c7956751be5d38b5c0cb2e09c0","text":"5 TB","correct":false},{"id":"3a6d03856b824be771cdd922375d59db","text":"20 GB","correct":false},{"id":"0d642755e7f12f7563e3db33bd0c39cb","text":"1 GB","correct":false},{"id":"70f79b00cb7649d94d473895d6c540d2","text":"1 TB","correct":false}]},{"id":"1azz6wyo-s13f-kikp-9zl7-obrtwc74xz52","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services should you use if you'd like to be notified when you have crossed a billing threshold?","explanation":"A CloudWatch alarm can be set to monitor spending on your AWS Account.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudwatch/","title":"About CloudWatch"}],"answers":[{"id":"726f0166d9c5880f1646439cf8ed64d3","text":"AWS Cost Allocation","correct":false},{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":true},{"id":"80550a5f8560e734862d7290c462206d","text":"AWS Budget","correct":false},{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":false}]},{"id":"a6f49f26-0fbc-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following pricing models are available for Amazon RDS?","explanation":"You can pay for Amazon RDS using either On-Demand or Reserved instance pricing.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/pricing/","title":"Amazon RDS Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"e26ff95de7b422fa8d7999578d2becc3","text":"On-Demand","correct":true},{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":true},{"id":"bda9eb7fcdccf237f87fb190ee3b4275","text":"Dedicated Server","correct":false},{"id":"6c9d6b8aea6f3d16847bdebe05878a2d","text":"Spot","correct":false}]},{"id":"g817t8h6-2yd3-mhf7-wf2v-n82br09qszt7","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following Compliance certifications attests to the security of the AWS platform regarding credit card transactions?","explanation":"PCI DSS is a compliance program which must be followed by any organizations handling Credit Card data. AWS has achieved a PCI Level 1 certification, the highest level available","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Compliance"}],"answers":[{"id":"faf72a9a0f8e7e240ee1346d6e2056e3","text":"SOC 1","correct":false},{"id":"7aa6bd3f5ca63135c1f75edd80d7a6ba","text":"SOC 2","correct":false},{"id":"74073bf9c7bfe155fe513fd4624ae2f2","text":"PCI DSS Level 1","correct":true},{"id":"7829c763646fba446ea5831ef095f756","text":"ISO 27001","correct":false}]},{"id":"7ed103d1-670b-487f-aa14-6d5e29084eb2","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following Amazon EC2 pricing models automatically adjusts charges as your usage changes?","explanation":"Savings Plans is the only Amazon EC2 pricing model that provides the flexibility of adjusting charges depending on the amount of usage, thereby saving money in the process.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/savingsplans/","title":"Savings Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"e26ff95de7b422fa8d7999578d2becc3","text":"On-Demand","correct":false},{"id":"b9912bfb6c79dc963ccc7e74d0ef9b36","text":"Savings Plan","correct":true},{"id":"acbe4e201e8e2ac67830983f9c8d7970","text":"Dedicated Hosts","correct":false},{"id":"29068f6044e3fedf44165e646a2d2bb1","text":"Reserved Instances","correct":false}]},{"id":"ipqdbu85-0egr-7f6l-daqk-ftz6657spa8l","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes a system that is always online — without the need for human intervention?","explanation":"A highly available system is one that is always online — without the need for human intervention. Although Fault Tolerance is closely related to High Availability, FT usually implies a degradation of service without human intervention, unlike HA which is like-for-like.","links":[{"url":"https://media.amazonwebservices.com/architecturecenter/AWS_ac_ra_ftha_04.pdf","title":"Fault Tolerance and High Availability Infographic"}],"answers":[{"id":"28cb2468ce3a85b4d10668ec48f5e4d6","text":"Scalable","correct":false},{"id":"9818cb0bfa2dfb200a8c078b1fe1c2fd","text":"Highly Available","correct":true},{"id":"a078ed5ade8df4aac54efbdb57e63ad2","text":"Elastic","correct":false},{"id":"35d7975974b40518da5e7f990c6a7d1d","text":"Fault Tolerant","correct":false}]},{"id":"0e20ce8c-1a57-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements is true of AWS Regions?","explanation":"AWS Regions are geographical areas that consist of locations called Availability Zones. Because they are isolated from each other, there is no automatic replication of resources between them. In addition, data transfer between Regions is not free; there is a charge associated with that.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-regions-availability-zones.html","title":"Regions, Availability Zones, and Local Zones"}],"answers":[{"id":"96676b55f4ae2e27083b81e373c80e5a","text":"They automatically replicate resources among each other.","correct":false},{"id":"3a4116551c9039850c094ec59ecc726c","text":"They are composed of Availability Zones.","correct":true},{"id":"6f99c65ce03a0a9018c608fc49149883","text":"There are no charges for data transferred between them.","correct":false},{"id":"f941bbe63c60384543e03468d67e8a94","text":"They are independent geographical areas.","correct":true}]},{"id":"ltl6jev0-2f05-xevd-rnut-yi3l7ar7nzk1","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to reliability?","explanation":"The elasticity of cloud computing means that you never need to over-provision or manage change at the resource level.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"25ddbfce9d53b8f5a9e09aad85948b96","text":"Stop guessing about your capacity requirements.","correct":true},{"id":"c57c5e34d89769a30ca48ef1c1155033","text":"Scale horizontally.","correct":true},{"id":"2c081b2e4ef662d134361511c0f138e1","text":"Manage change at the individual resource level.","correct":false},{"id":"7f20528f07a394778f02e20e5453fc02","text":"When in doubt, over-provision.","correct":false}]},{"id":"uvop23ho-2fn6-04p8-5luy-ybljxy0o0477","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following services helps you to deliver your content to your customers faster?","explanation":"Amazon CloudFront is a content delivery network that speeds the delivery of content to your users.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/","title":"About CloudFront"}],"answers":[{"id":"34bc95906489c2d5c9583e3230cd48b2","text":"Elastic Block Store","correct":false},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":false},{"id":"02f85544eeded6ef1b6c40d62bcadddd","text":"Amazon Elastic File System","correct":false},{"id":"bef6cb89241de238f082cb243307ad1b","text":"CloudFront","correct":true}]},{"id":"rqfj1uaw-51ci-mvl2-1djk-uzefaek5cehy","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is correct?","explanation":"The number of Edge Locations is greater than the number of Availability Zones, which is greater than the number of Regions. Regions contain Availability Zones, therefore there will always be more AZs than Regions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"3782de3e5fc87f6e1a21193778c0d5bf","text":"# of Availability Zones > # of Edge Locations > # of Regions","correct":false},{"id":"916cfd186ad7a451ebd785b35c738429","text":"# of Edge Locations > # of Availability Zones > # of Regions","correct":true},{"id":"07ebe9ccf5e5396c2f2c81de53d3829e","text":"# of Regions > # of Availability Zones > # of Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"27268ba761c3ae0dbf9e4c8959f13e0f","text":"# of Availability Zones > # of Regions > # of Edge Locations","correct":false}]},{"id":"zlyf2s8s-kula-sxtl-s07a-i3uh455n1hnu","domain":"security","question":"Which credentials can you use to access the AWS Management console?","explanation":"You use a username and password to log into the AWS console, although Access key and Secret Access key can be used to access some APIs programmatically","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/console/","title":"The AWS Management Console"}],"answers":[{"id":"be677306ceb7d966e7a06ee1bf387acf","text":"Your Access key","correct":false},{"id":"afc76c6d8222878e0449abb2ea16838f","text":"Your Username and Password","correct":true},{"id":"4dd4dfb52929ef230415ada1a4169dc1","text":"Your Security Token","correct":false},{"id":"2a7454c71a60c06ab2189283f1788e09","text":"Your Secret Access key","correct":false}]},{"id":"7a194fa6-5966-4548-9b32-ac602a517ac8","domain":"concepts","question":"With AWS services, you can use as many resources as you need, as well as use them when you need them. Which of the following terms can be applied to this concept?","explanation":"Working in a traditional infrastructure environment means that you have to deal with fixed resources, which is comparatively costly and labor-intensive. By contrast, AWS services are much more convenient; the services provide the ability to use as many resources as you need and dispose of them when you no longer need them. That’s why such resources are both temporary and disposable.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"5936fc4450b6f3f75cc6fe08d2890b77","text":"Temporary resources","correct":true},{"id":"83ec702ebd8e13f87318dba136356773","text":"Dedicated resources","correct":false},{"id":"e035a6f9ed7c8c3c99e48b95e32cc364","text":"Fixed resources","correct":false},{"id":"fd3ca13906a4c1e05f791d27dbc66914","text":"Disposable resources","correct":true}]},{"id":"3a04d665-f391-4b59-93bc-8e7e60565b99","domain":"tech","question":"Your project manager (PM) tasked you with launching an instance for a web application to be developed for an NGO. The PM is especially interested in using an AWS service that provides predicable monthly pricing, and he expects the instance to have the ability to burst above the baseline level of CPU performance when needed. What AWS service should you use to launch this instance?","explanation":"Although EC2 could have been the correct answer, two things are key here: Predicable monthly pricing and instance ability to burst above the baseline level of CPU performance when needed. Lightsail accomplishes that; EC2 is more suitable for consistently high CPU performance, and costs vary according to usage.","links":[{"url":"https://lightsail.aws.amazon.com/ls/docs/en_us/articles/amazon-lightsail-frequently-asked-questions-faq","title":"Frequently Asked Questions in Amazon Lightsail"}],"answers":[{"id":"b21eea42e76007ac061cf37a5a41037d","text":"Lightsail","correct":true},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"1dd30e8d60c2a200781dbcc9286f0919","text":"Elasticsearch Service","correct":false},{"id":"bef6cb89241de238f082cb243307ad1b","text":"CloudFront","correct":false}]},{"id":"2cp5w12s-zexu-46ts-0im3-vuthjxgjujs3","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes the ability to scale computing resources up or down easily, while only paying for the resources used?","explanation":"Elasticity describes the ability to scale computing resources up or down easily, while only paying for the resources used.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"fb76c61f626c7fb0fd2ee1226e9fd8bd","text":"Fault-tolerance","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":true}]},{"id":"rc4dwp79-ix5s-h912-sdcj-9gmmhl6zacte","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following is AWS' managed DDoS protection service?","explanation":"AWS Shield is AWS' managed DDoS protection service at Layer 4. AWS WAF provides protection from common exploits against your web applications at Layer 7, and does not protect against DDoS attacks.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/shield/?nc2=h_l3_dm","title":"About AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":true},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":false}]},{"id":"f073f45a-0541-43a5-a1ae-4c67afb87086","domain":"security","question":"As an AWS customer, what is the best thing to do if you want to get periodic official statements to be notified of security and privacy events with AWS services?","explanation":"You will not get official security statements from the AWS News Blog, which provides current events regarding AWS. And while you can always send an email to request security announcements, chances are you will be redirected to the Security Bulletins page, where you can subscribe to an RSS feed to be updated on security and privacy issues.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/security/security-bulletins/?card-body.sort-by=item.additionalFields.bulletinDateSort&card-body.sort-order=desc","title":"Security Bulletins"}],"answers":[{"id":"ab09f1b93a71ea2e9b2634438d8c954a","text":"Email AWS Security to express your interest in receiving security announcements.","correct":false},{"id":"ddd4a6bf26b1483b9221e364d190454f","text":"Email AWS directly to express your interest in receiving security announcements.","correct":false},{"id":"335ec04e733ed7b0bacd46bf6948b866","text":"Subscribe to the AWS Security Bulletin RSS feed.","correct":true},{"id":"520267b96af385f180fa3fd9ec26dc51","text":"Subscribe to the AWS News Blog.","correct":false}]},{"id":"c6jepoji-nqyo-0t96-juj8-ob2lymloevj9","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the AWS Assurance Program?","explanation":"Certifications/Attestations and Compliance with Laws and Regulations are cornerstones of the of the AWS Assurance Program.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Assurance"}],"answers":[{"id":"506afacef0a47cc7635b5cf0a3476c31","text":"Certifications/Attestations","correct":true},{"id":"4dc626268903b46b79d0a76e0a989cf8","text":"Partner Validations","correct":false},{"id":"fc0d934854b825185d4ea2079edf68c3","text":"Compliance with Laws and Regulations","correct":true},{"id":"19d78b92947f957cca4c7698118fdb82","text":"Following industry best practices","correct":false},{"id":"de208db5a32df9befe2ed7f080863f9e","text":"Customer Testimonials","correct":false}]},{"id":"9n50o6rz-03s4-bpbd-i7dy-36qby4h0ka5x","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when running an RDS database on AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance), as well as making sure the underlying OS and application is up to date. You as the user are responsible for keeping your data secure.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"8782b4a6bdea28cea082df1413a7f818","text":"Controlling access to the compute hardware","correct":false},{"id":"57b862a3c428d3330f8c03216acd2c16","text":"Controlling access to the database","correct":true},{"id":"2b6b76aaf679124f3da7b20c5df23923","text":"Updating the database software","correct":false},{"id":"0266c79a8678f6881cc2857043b46509","text":"Controlling access to the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"86da12905838c932b65844a3fa01aa08","text":"Updating the operating system","correct":false}]},{"id":"pjzmsz8b-2lx2-8zb8-wauh-od1x4h0ja4pd","domain":"tech","question":"A new System Administrator has started with your organisation and requires a user account so that they can manage you AWS resources. You have AWS resources in multiple regions - what needs to be done to allow the new starter access to manage resources in the regions you operate in?","explanation":"Any answer that suggest a role is incorrect as roles by themselves will not let a user log in. The correct approach is to create an IAM user - and as IAM is a global service - configuration in IAM applies globally, not just regionally, only a single IAM user account is required.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction.html","title":"What is IAM"}],"answers":[{"id":"f854b98dd0b3ff05864e11c45979706b","text":"Create a single IAM user account - this will enable access in all regions","correct":true},{"id":"98cddae0b6f5dfe1792d38678a9851a0","text":"Create an IAM role in each region that you have resources in - this will enable access in per region","correct":false},{"id":"15ed84de219d4333fe7069904bec4dbc","text":"Create an IAM user account in each region that you have resources in - this will enable access in per region","correct":false},{"id":"2effe9ac093a8dcafdd02f3e97c1244e","text":"Create a single IAM role - this will enable access in all regions","correct":false}]},{"id":"cf545dc9-39ca-4eec-869f-0d416b59aa1f","domain":"concepts","question":"Adding resources to your application as user demand grows is an example of which cloud concept?","explanation":"Scalability is the concept that as cloud has essentially limitless capacity, it allows you to expand out as needed - as detailed in the question. Automation relates to simplyfying common repeated tasks and removing the human element. Although elasticity (the ability to go up and down in resources as needed) is related, this question specifically ask for in in response to user demand, which is closer to Scalability. High Availability relates to the ability of your application to withstand failures in Cloud Infrastructure.","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false}]},{"id":"e08137aa-20a0-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following describes a subnet?","explanation":"A virtual private cloud, or VPC, is the virtual network you create in your AWS account. When you create a VPC, you split it into smaller network segments by specifying a range of IP addresses. These segments are referred to as subnets, and this is where you launch your AWS resources.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/what-is-amazon-vpc.html","title":"What Is Amazon VPC?"}],"answers":[{"id":"341f92e23cc01405941735e106cc5b82","text":"A range of IP addresses in the virtual private cloud","correct":true},{"id":"35b8947d693a814719c463b699fee868","text":"A subsection of the Internet","correct":false},{"id":"79da4a3447f86eaa72f611a8d8a1d4cc","text":"A private connection to the virtual private cloud","correct":false},{"id":"5e57bdce4ee3d720c44022ab3a1989dc","text":"A virtual network dedicated to an AWS account","correct":false}]},{"id":"d65c52f9-7f9b-4765-b0a6-cf58294f7034","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements is false regarding Amazon ElastiCache?","explanation":"All statements are correct about ElastiCache save for one. ElasticCache is designed to streamline read operations. Write operations cannot be performed with Elasticache","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonElastiCache/latest/APIReference/Welcome.html","title":"Amazon ElastiCache"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonElastiCache/latest/red-ug/WhatIs.html","title":"What is Amazon ElastiCache for Redis?"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonElastiCache/latest/mem-ug/WhatIs.html","title":"What is Amazon ElastiCache for Memcached?"}],"answers":[{"id":"77f82ce3947b78092c1bc9c5bd5cc7f0","text":"It is used for making write operations to databases significantly faster three open-source in-memory caching engines.","correct":true},{"id":"0cb5de3d769c0ce3b66cea646faab2ea","text":"It saves common queries to enable faster retrieval of information than disk-based databases.","correct":false},{"id":"b16ed17379f1b31504154714e5bb941a","text":"It makes it easier to set up, operate, and scale a distributed cache in the cloud.","correct":false},{"id":"bad6e5cdf0a4beb80181a0a2cf2f5793","text":"It reduces the administrative burden that comes with launching and managing a distributed cache.","correct":false}]},{"id":"520b9022-2fa7-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Your company needs the support of concierge-level account specialists to help with billing and account subjects. Which of the following AWS Support pricing plans provides that feature?","explanation":"Only the Enterprise support plan will provide a Concierge Support Team, which is a group of account specialists to assist your company with their billing and accounting questions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"AWS Support Plans"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/enterprise/","title":"AWS Enterprise Support"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false}]},{"id":"npfixa13-rww8-6ifs-mar3-1z12ny6vwzat","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following services will help you optimize your entire AWS environment in real-time following AWS best practices?","explanation":"Trusted Advisor helps you optimize your entire AWS environment in real-time following AWS best practices. It helps you optimize cost, fault-tolerance, and more.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":true},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":false}]},{"id":"1db22272-d476-4034-844a-5d8d9fd40091","domain":"concepts","question":"A telecommunications company has his hired you as a consultant to develop a business case for moving its IT applications and infrastructure to AWS. The company’s leadership understands the agility value of the cloud, but the finance group is not interested in shifting capital expense to operating expense due to the company’s tax structure. What will you include in the business case to attempt to satisfy everyone at the company?","explanation":"Many companies capitalize reserved instance purchases, especially those with 3-year terms. Waiting for current infrastructure to fully depreciate will cause the company to miss the other cloud benefits that are available. Moving the company to an operating expense model will prove too large a task, and will most likely result in a rejected business case. Elastic infrastructure is definitely a benefit, but doesn't address the capitalization issue.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws_pricing_overview.pdf","title":"How AWS Pricing Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"cd56c0654f075d81e563f7f6740b2cb8","text":"Show the value of an elastic infrastructure for avoiding wasted capacity","correct":false},{"id":"875be7dcedf2167b7fa3192f4c94b2a3","text":"Suggest that the company make reserved instance purchases and capitalize them","correct":true},{"id":"b55403f80a04df0f30d6552d35188c46","text":"Suggest that the company wait to migrate to AWS until the current infrastructure is fully depreciated","correct":false},{"id":"8419aa56459afcd14644026053cc0cfc","text":"Show the company the TCO value of moving to an operating expense model","correct":false}]},{"id":"ef32cbf3-49b8-406a-aa2d-eaff05300839","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Edge locations are a part of AWS' content distribution network, and are separate from Regions and AZs. The number of Edge Locations around the world is greater than that of Regions and Availability Zones, in order to reduce latency between your content and your customers - the more that exist, the greater the chance there is one where you need it.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"5810cb8fea9cc8e7773f9cc96fdd6c51","text":"There are more Regions than Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"b8ecf41dfa2a8f2d576a9407c87dadf5","text":"There are more Availability Zones then Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"9fe244cde3895fdb2a60650e6154c15b","text":"The number of Availability Zones is the same as the number of Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"78f3c24434277d629cc0a0d14f18c598","text":"There are more Edge locations than Availability zones","correct":true}]},{"id":"b386cdc3-9626-47e1-9be3-a4d78c363ad4","domain":"security","question":"Instead of relying on a single data center to provide its services across the world, AWS relies on several physical locations, each of which consists of one or more data centers. What are the official names for these physical locations and data centers?","explanation":"The physical locations from which AWS provides its services are known as Regions. Each Region consists of at least two Availability Zone, which can have anywhere from one data center to several of them.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/","title":"Global Infrastructures Regions and AZs"}],"answers":[{"id":"02da4e23b021b2dfa7ed963444ab3325","text":"Locations; data centers","correct":false},{"id":"fb27078790943273979b82fd00f61dd1","text":" Sections; Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"c4bc6e143511ce56ce0ac41624e4c370","text":"Regions; Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"2015015e824f6bbbc098e8b097d2dbda","text":"Regions; data centers","correct":false}]},{"id":"6rxg9wr0-2vdy-xb2h-ds26-ul6n2c6g8bnu","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support plans feature access to AWS support via email only during business hours?","explanation":"The Developer support plan features access to AWS support during business hours via email. Business and Enterprise support plans allow 24x7 email support. The Basic support plan includes no email support options. Because the question specifies support *only* during business hours, there is only one correct answer.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":true},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false}]}]}}}}
